(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T11:33:46.187357",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey! everytime I'm so proud of you
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと近づいてほ・し・い
I want you to get closer,
どんなことも話してほしいのよ！
I want you to talk to me about anything!
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
出来そうもない（くらいな）こ・と
Though there's nothing I can't do,
おねだりしてくれていいよ
it's okay if you coax me a bit.
ずっとあこがれてた人と
With the person I've admired for so long,
再開した
we've reunited.
運命感じなきゃウソだよ
Gotta feel that it's fate, or it's a lie!
Now！Touch my heart！
Now! Touch my heart!
100年経って地球が変わっても
Even if 100 years pass and the Earth changes,
気持ちは変わらないわ
my feelings won't change,
愛の園
Garden of love.
Now！Touch my heart！
Now! Touch my heart!
1年経って私が邪魔ならば
If I'm in your way after 1 year,
良い子の私は bye bye
it's bye bye to the good girl in me!
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you.
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと近づいて欲しい
I want you to get closer,
どんなことも話して欲しいのよ！
I want you to talk to me about anything!
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
出来るそうもないくらいのこと
Even with things I could never do,
おねだりしてくれていいよ
it's okay if you ask me for them.
ずっと憧れてた人と再会した
I've reunited with the person I always admired.
運命感じなきゃ嘘だよ
If I didn't feel fate, that would be a lie.
Now! Touch my heart
100年たって地球が変わっても
even if 100 years pass and the Earth changes,
気持ちはかわらないわ 愛の園
my feelings won't change, the garden of love.
Now! Touch my heart
一年たって私が邪魔ならば よいこのさんは Bye bye
if after a year I'm a nuisance, this good girl says bye-bye.
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you.
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと意地悪でいいよ
It's okay if you're even meaner.
過去も未来も あなたの自由でしょ！
Past and future are entirely your freedom!
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
夢は夢というの？
Do you call dreams just dreams?
あなたの夢を知りたい
I want to know about your dreams.
ずっと忘れない夜が続いているわ
Unforgettable nights keep continuing on.
運命抱きしめて眠るわ
I'll sleep holding onto fate.
Now! Touch my heart
1000年たって宇宙で暮らしても
even if 1,000 years pass and we live in space,
私はかわらないわ 愛の園
I won't change, the garden of love.
Now! Touch my heart
明日になって私が邪魔ならば よいこの私は Bye bye
if tomorrow I'm a nuisance, this good girl says bye-bye.
Now! Touch my heart
1000年たって宇宙で暮らしても
even if 1,000 years pass and we live in space,
私はかわらないわ 愛の園
I won't change, the garden of love.
Now! Touch my heart
明日になって私が邪魔ならば よいこの私は Bye bye
if tomorrow I'm a nuisance, this good girl says bye-bye.
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you.
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
Let's go! One, two!
One, two! One, two!
Now! Touch my heart
1000年たって宇宙で暮らしても
even if 1,000 years pass and we live in space,
私はかわらないわ 愛の園
I won't change, the garden of love.
Now! Touch my heart
明日になって私が邪魔ならば よいこの私は Bye bye
if tomorrow I'm a nuisance, this good girl says bye-bye.
Hey! Every time, I'm so proud of you.
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと意地悪でいいよ
It's okay if you're even meaner.
過去も未来も あなたの自由でしょ！
Past and future are entirely your freedom!
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
夢は夢というの？
Do you call dreams just dreams?
あなたの夢を知りたい
I want to know about your dreams.
ずっと忘れない夜が続いているわ
Unforgettable nights keep continuing on.
運命抱きしめて眠るわ
I'll sleep holding onto fate.
Now! Touch my heart
1000年たって宇宙で暮らしても
even if 1,000 years pass and we live in space,
私はかわらないわ 愛の園
I won't change, the garden of love.
Now! Touch my heart
明日になって私が邪魔ならば よいこの私は Bye bye
if tomorrow I'm a nuisance, this good girl says bye-bye.
Hikari-kyaa! And welcome to Kiara's Birthday Festival, English Mates!
And welcome to my Birthday for Ely live today!
The first song was an iconic, relatively old song from Morning Musume called "Ai no Sono".
Yeah, did you like it?
There was like some funny moves. It's just like... what am I?
Yeah! So, as you can see, today once again I'm doing a Hello Project cover song birthday festival.
Um, it's my second time to do like a Hello Project cover song themed live.
Did you watch the last one? I hope you did.
And back then, there were a bunch of songs that I felt like, "Ah, I still want to do so badly!"
And that's why we're here today.
And yeah, so a lot of Hello Project songs to look forward to.
Also, ta-da! Hashtag #KiaraBday2026.
Please use it, make me famous, take some screenshots, some clips, tell the internet about this.
Um, also let's talk a little bit about the background. What is this, you might wonder?
If you have watched a lot of Hello Project music videos in your life, you might actually recognize this because it's from a Morning Musume song.
Um, maybe an upcoming song? Maybe after this?
So we will have corners today! We are starting right now with the Morning Musume corner, and then we'll have other corners too.
And for each corner, there will be like a representative backdrop.
Like this one! So, please pay attention to the different variations of the stages today.
And now I'm kind of sad because I think I have solo and I want some friends to come and help me perform.
So, shall we begin and continue with the next song?
Yes, yes! Bring in the ladies!
Come on, come on, come on, come on
笑った顔をして返事した
I answered with a smiling face,
あなたが嘘をつく合図だね
which is the sign that you're going to lie.
笑った顔をして返事した
Smiling, I answered you back
あなたがウソをつく合図だね
That's your sign you're gonna lie to me
2年目の記念日を前にして
Just before our second anniversary
私が振られちゃって終わるのね
This'll all end with you dumping me
「また一人ぼっち マリコ」
“You're single again, Mariko”
気付かないふりをしていつまでも
Guess I’ll pretend not to know, as long as I want
抱きしめられていようかな
As I stay here in your arms
ああ あなたが優しいのわかってる
Oh, you’re a nice guy, I know
けどその分つらすぎるの
That just makes it hurt all the more
お祈りをしたけれど
Even though I said a prayer
心は遠く離れてゆく
Our hearts keep growing far apart
ああ 私からお別れ告げようと
Oh, I’ll break up with you myself
そう思ったけどできない
Yeah, or at least I wanted to, but couldn’t
会話の中で何度も
Although multiple times as we talk
タイミングみてたけど
I’ve been trying to find the right time
抱きしめられたままでいようかな
Can I just stay in your arms like this?
ああ あなたが優しいのわかってる
Oh, you’re a nice guy, I know
けどその分つらすぎるの
That just makes it hurt all the more
お祈りをしたけれど
Even though I said a prayer
心は遠く離れてゆく
Our hearts keep growing far apart
ああ 私からお別れ告げようと
Oh, I’ll break up with you myself
そう思ったけどできない
Yeah, or at least I wanted to, but couldn’t
会話の中で何度も
Although multiple times as we talk
タイミングみてたけど
I’ve been trying to find the right time
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry
かも
Maybe
かも かも
Maybe, maybe
どうしてそんなに無理するの
Why do you always push yourself so hard?
嫌ならお別れを言ってよね
If you don't want to, break up with me
わざとわがままをしてみたけど
I whined like a baby for something on purpose
優しく笑顔で答える人
But you're the type to smile sweetly in response
「もうこれでいいの？ マリコ」
“You're okay with this, Mariko?”
自問自答をする私
I wonder to myself
最後だって言う前に抱きしめて
Before I say it's over, hold me
ねえ ねえ 冷たくていいから
C'mon, c'mon. It's cold out, so it's fine
そのあなたの優しさが罪なのよ
Your kindness is a transgression
ほら 決心にぶくなる
See? It's giving me second thoughts
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we met
毎日確かめ合いたい
I wanna check with each other daily
ああ もう少しこのままでいたいけど
Oh, I'd love to stay a bit longer
そう あなたといいたいけれど
Yeah, I'd love to stay here with you
最後の夜が来たら
If our last night's on the way
強気なフリしながら
Then while acting all confident…
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry
かも
Maybe
かも かも
Maybe, maybe
そのあなたの優しさが罪なのよ
Your kindness is a transgression
ほら 決心にぶくなる
See? It's giving me second thoughts
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we met
毎日確かめ合いたい
I wanna check with each other daily
ああ もう少しこのままでいたいけど
Oh, I'd love to stay a bit longer
そう あなたといいたいけれど
Yeah, I'd love to stay here with you
最後の夜が来たら
If our last night's on the way
強気なフリしながら
Then while acting all confident…
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry
かも
Maybe
かも かも
Maybe, maybe
早く 逢いたいよ
I want to meet you soon...
早く あなたに逢いたい
Hey, I want to meet you soon...
「はやく会いたいのは・・・ ねえ はやく 貴方に会いたい」
I want to meet soon... Hey, I want to meet you soon...
先に向かってるROAD
There's a road ahead of us
「はやく会いたいのに… ねえ はやく 貴方に会いたい」
"I want to see you soon... Hey, I want to see you soon."
YA-HEY HO
先に向かってるROAD
The ROAD heading forward
止まらないミュージック
The music that won't stop
恋人からの花束
A bouquet from my lover
真夜中届くメール
An email arriving at midnight
女の子なら 誰でも思う
If you're a girl, everyone thinks of it
HAPPY END STORY
やさしくされりゃ
If you're treated gently,
うれしいけど
I'm happy, but
限りなく求めちゃう
I want more without limit
色っぽい キュピット
Sexy Cupid
じれったい キスもっと
Impatient, give me more kisses
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
Of the hot heartbeat, SEXY ISLAND
笑ってる星も
The laughing stars too
気取ってる午後も
The acting haughty afternoon too
この愛を見届けてほしい
I want you to watch over this love
YA-HEY HO
海が輝いて ジェラシー
The sea is shining, jealousy
独り言の週末
A weekend of talking to myself
あなたといたならうれしい
If I were with you, I'd be happy
不思議な匂いSWEETIE
A mysterious scent, SWEETIE
寂しい夜と
A lonely night and
楽しい時間
A fun time
HAPPY END STORY
もう一度言うわ
I'll say it again
大好きです
I love you
抱きしめて 離さないで
Hold me, don't let me go
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit
じれったい ミスショット
Impatient, mis-shot
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
It will last forever, SEXY ISLAND
愛して 急接近
Love me, sudden approach
未来に 大接近
To the future, big approach
どこまでも 抱きしめて
I want you to hold me forever
欲しい
I want you
色っぽい キュピット
Sexy Cupid
じれったい キスもっと
Impatient, give me more kisses
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
Of the hot heartbeat, SEXY ISLAND
笑ってる星も
The laughing stars too
気取ってる午後も
The acting haughty afternoon too
この愛を見届けてほしい
I want you to watch over this love
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit
じれったい ミスショット
Impatient, mis-shot
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
It will last forever, SEXY ISLAND
愛して 急接近
Love me, sudden approach
未来に 大接近
To the future, big approach
どこまでも 抱きしめて
I want you to hold me forever
欲しい
I want you
YA-HEY HO
Isaki Riona
Koganei Niko
Mizumiya Su
Rindo Chihaya
Kikirara Vivi
渋谷を歩く
Walking around Shibuya
一人で歩く
Walking alone
人ごみの中
In the crowd
大好きなあの人探す
I search for that person I love
渋谷を歩く
I walk around Shibuya,
一人で歩く
walking alone
人ごみの中
through the crowd,
大好きなあの人探す
searching for the one I love.
手を繋いでいい
"Can we hold hands?"
その想いから
Driven by that feeling,
わざとはぐれて
I purposely got separated—
みただけなの
just to see what would happen.
泣きそう
I feel like crying;
こんな私をどうか離さないでね
please don't ever let me go.
恋する想いが (my ダリング)
My love for you (my darling)
大きく膨らみ (i love you)
swells up big (I love you).
考えすぎたら (my ダリング)
If I think too much (my darling),
空回りしちゃうな (i love you)
I end up going in circles (I love you).
まだまだ私は (my ダリング)
I'm still (my darling)
あなたが怖いわ (i love you)
afraid of you (I love you).
きっといつの日か (my ダリング)
I'm sure one day (my darling)
嫌われちゃいそうで (i love you)
you'll end up hating me (I love you).
ああ
Ah...
あなたを見つけ
When I found you,
涙が出ちゃった
I burst into tears.
少し前から
You said you'd noticed me
私に気付いていなかったなんて
a little while before that—
少しずるいよ
that's kind of mean,
だけど言えない
but I can't say it.
最初のきっかけは 私だし
After all, I was the one who started it.
どうしよう
What should I do?
うつむいてたら
As I hung my head,
手を握ってくれたわ
you reached out and took my hand.
大人になっても (my ダリング)
Even when we grow up (my darling)
もっとその先も (i love you)
and far beyond that (I love you),
腰が曲がっても (my ダリング)
even when we're old and bent (my darling),
手を繋ぐときには
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう (my ダリング)
I'm sure my heart will race (my darling),
恥ずかしいでしょう (i love you)
and I'll feel so shy (I love you).
それでも私を (my ダリング)
Still, please hold me close (my darling)
やさしく包んでね (i love you)
and gently wrap me in your arms (I love you).
大人になっても (my ダリング)
Even when we grow up (my darling)
もっとその先も (i love you)
and far beyond that (I love you),
腰が曲がっても (my ダリング)
even when we're old and bent (my darling),
手を繋ぐときには
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう (my ダリング)
I'm sure my heart will race (my darling),
恥ずかしいでしょう (i love you)
and I'll feel so shy (I love you).
大人になっても (my ダリング)
Even when we grow up (my darling)
もっとその先も (i love you)
and far beyond that (I love you),
腰が曲がっても (my ダリング)
even when we're old and bent (my darling),
手を繋ぐときには
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう (my ダリング)
I'm sure my heart will race (my darling),
恥ずかしいでしょう (i love you)
and I'll feel so shy (I love you).
それでも私を (my ダリング)
Still, please hold me close (my darling)
やさしく包んでね (i love you)
and gently wrap me in your arms (I love you).
それでも私を (my ダリング)
Still, please hold me close (my darling)
やさしく包んでね (i love you)
and gently wrap me in your arms (I love you).
大人になっても (my ダリング)
Even when we grow up (my darling)
もっとその先も (i love you)
and far beyond that (I love you),
腰が曲がっても (my ダリング)
even when we're old and bent (my darling),
手を繋ぐときには
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう (my ダリング)
I'm sure my heart will race (my darling),
恥ずかしいでしょう (i love you)
and I'll feel so shy (I love you).
それでも私を (my ダリング)
Still, please hold me close (my darling)
やさしく包んでね (i love you)
and gently wrap me in your arms (I love you).
大人になっても (my ダリング)
Even when we grow up (my darling)
もっとその先も (i love you)
and far beyond that (I love you),
腰が曲がっても (my ダリング)
even when we're old and bent (my darling),
手を繋ぐときには
whenever we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょう (my ダリング)
I'm sure my heart will race (my darling),
恥ずかしいでしょう (i love you)
and I'll feel so shy (I love you).
それでも私を (my ダリング)
Still, please hold me close (my darling)
やさしく包んでね (i love you)
and gently wrap me in your arms (I love you).
強情
Stubborn,
あなたは強情
you're so stubborn,
わからず屋のままね
still being clueless.
もう付き合いきれない
I can't put up with this anymore.
サヨナラ愛人
Goodbye, my love.
友情
Friendship?
「友情」なんて戻れるわけないでしょ
There's no way we can go back to being friends.
この先もわがままに振り回すつもり
I intend to keep being selfish from here on, too.
浮気なら
If you were cheating,
それなりに許すつもりだった
I intended to forgive you for that.
プライドを傷つけた
But I can't forgive you
あの日は許さない
for the day you hurt my pride.
涙 止めぬ涙
Tears, my tears won't stop,
これでスッキリするわ
but this will refresh me.
あなたを信じていた
Believing in you that day
あの日がもったいない ah
was such a waste, ah.
それでも愛していた
Even so, I loved you.
あなたとのサヨナラ
Goodbye to being with you.
動揺
Unrest—
心の隙間
in the gaps of my heart,
風邪をひきそうだけど
I feel like I'm catching a cold,
それならすぐ治るし…
but that will heal quickly...
サヨナラ愛人
Goodbye, my love.
涙 想い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears,
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私も強情ね
I'm stubborn too,
今頃そう思うわ
or so I think now.
あんなに愛していた
You whom I loved so much—
あなたとのサヨナラ ah
this is my goodbye with you, ah.
愛してて あなたとのさようなら
Loving you, and saying goodbye to you...
心のすきま 風をひきそうだけど
Though there's a draft in my empty heart...
それならすぐ直るし さようなら愛しいひと
It'll heal right away. Farewell, my beloved.
白状しよう 怒いばれても 夜を戻せないから
Let's confess, even if I'm scolded, because I can't turn back the night.
もう電話は出ないわ どんなに寂しくても
I won't answer the phone anymore, no matter how lonely I get.
いつもより早いいけど ベッドに入るわ
I'll go to bed earlier than usual.
懐かしい記憶との 戦いの時間
Time of battle with nostalgic memories.
涙 思い出 涙 悲しくなんか無いよ
Tears, memories, tears, I'm not sad at all.
私もごちそうね 今ごろそう思うわ
I'm having a treat right now, I think.
あんなに愛してて あなたとのさようなら
Loving you so much, and saying goodbye to you.
涙 止まらぬ涙 これできっとスルーわ
Tears, unstoppable tears, this will surely get through.
あなたを信じてた あの日がもう耐えない
I believed in you, that day is no longer bearable.
涙 思い出 涙 悲しくなんか無いよ
Tears, memories, tears, I'm not sad at all.
私もごちそうね 今ごろそう思うわ
I'm having a treat right now, I think.
あんなに愛してて あなたとのさようなら
Loving you so much, and saying goodbye to you.
That was Forever Love and Namida no Iro with Flow Glow!
It's like I'm a member of Flow Glow!
Hello everyone! My name is Riona! I'm Flow Glow's purapura yey! Relaxed girl!
Hello everyone! My name is Riona! I'm Flow Glow's relaxed girl!
My name is Kohana Nico, Flow Glow's comedian modoki!
My name is Kohana Nico, Flow Glow's comedy wannabe!
Big car, Risuya, yay!
Four girls, DJ and driver, Rindo Chihaya!
ぷぷぷぷぺこら！
P-P-P-Pekora!
アイム凄yo キキララビビで
I'm Sugeyo! Kikirara Bibitê!
Well, when I chose to do these songs, I really wanted to bring in Frogol because...
Well, when I chose to do these songs, I really wanted to bring in Frogol...
because I know they're all really good at dancing. And performing...
全部！全部ダンス簡単だった！
All of it! All the dances were easy!
え、でもかっこよかった。みんななんか振るの見たときに、めっちゃかっこよいてなりました。
Everyone looked so cool doing the choreography!
私も、なんかそのみんなでどんどん出来上がって、完成度が高くなっていくうちに、
And as everyone came together and the level of completion got higher,
もう幸せすぎて！やばい！
I was just too happy! It's crazy!
いつも「え、かっこいい」って言ってくれてて、嬉しかった。
Everyone kept saying "You look so cool," which made me so happy.
なんかカノンで結構、こう、こういうの踏んだりとか、あんまり今までなくて、だからキアラ先輩にね、呼んでもらってそれができて嬉しかったです。
We don't usually do canon steps like this, so I was so happy Kiara-senpai invited me.
そうだね、なんか、あの、順番で回るとか、結構多くて、大変でした。
There were lots of parts taking turns rotating, so it was pretty tough.
すいません、難しい振り付け。あの、みなさんのコーナーは、キョウトのコーナーであって、キョウトっていうグループは、ダンスがマジでいつも難しいですよね。
Kyoto always has seriously difficult dances. Sorry about that!
実力派。ごめんね、でもみんなよくできてて、めっちゃ楽しかった！
True skill! But everyone did a great job and it was so much fun.
キュウトと言えば、アイウォントノウ、みんなの好きヘロプロの曲。知りたいけど、
Speaking of Cute, I want to know everyone's favorite Hello! Project song.
じゃあまず、あり...ありますか？ アモレヴィ、アモレヴィ！ 大好き！
First, are there any? Amorevy, Amorevy! I love it!
いいですね、最近の曲ですね。いいですね。あと、ニコタマ？
That's nice, recent songs. Also, Nikotama?
ニコタマ、バカヤロー、自分大切、大好きです。大好き。
Nikotama, Bakayaro, Jibun Taisetsu, I love them!
よね、すごキャラ好き。わかる、と、結構オタクのときって、
Right, I love Sugokyara. And as an otaku...
そう、私の好きな曲はモーニング娘。ワンフーさんの『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』。好き、やばい、本当大好き！
My favorite is Morning Musume's "Jikuu wo Koe Uchu wo Koe". I love it!
時空を超え、宇宙を超えて、すごい。しっとりの曲。
"Jikuu wo Koe Uchu wo Koe", amazing. A touching song.
S/mileage
Inugami Korone
Usada Pekora
Watson Amelia
いまもかつてないような
Unlike ever before,
キラキラした毎日
sparkling every day,
ぶっちぎり有頂天な日々送ってる
I'm having such ecstatic, runaway days.
恋をすれば勉強が
When I'm in love, I can't study
手につかない毎日
at all day by day.
恋のせいにしちゃって…ないっ！
Blaming it on love... no way!
今日はデート 彼と am 10:00に待ち合わせしてるの
Today is a date, meeting him at 10:00 AM.
wow wow
今日香りを少し変えた事気付くかしら君は
I wonder if you'll notice my changed scent today.
wow wow
ドクターストップがかかる程「恋落ち」してるわ
I've fallen so in love a doctor would stop me!
大好きが止まらない
My deep love just won't stop.
oh love me love me love me love me love me do!
wow wow
カルチャーショックを起こす程時代を変えるわ
Shaking up the culture so much we'll change the era!
スポットライトを浴びる二人口づけをしましょう！
The two of us in the spotlight, let's share a kiss!
i love you!
それでもたま雨降り
Even so, sometimes it rains,
ケンカもそりゃしますわ
and of course we have our fights.
ぶっちぎりこの世の終わりって感じね
It feels like the absolute end of the world.
仲直りのタイミングお互い様探って
We search for the right timing to make up,
週末にはデートしている
and go on a date over the weekend.
ランチタイム
Lunch time!
どの店にするかジャンケンで決める
Deciding which restaurant with rock-paper-scissors.
wow wow
そう本当は全部決めてくれてもいいのよ君が
Actually, I'd be fine if you decided everything.
wow wow
10パーセントの焼きもちは愛の裏返し
Ten percent jealousy is the flip side of love.
世界を変えてよ
Change the world!
oh love me love me love me love me love me do!
wow wow
100パーセントの愛情はウソなんかないよ
One hundred percent affection has no lies at all.
夢見る15歳
Dreaming 15-year-old,
どんな女の子には秘密の恋のボタンがあるのよ
Every girl has a secret button for love, you know.
今年の夏は負けない
This summer, I won't lose!
去年見た君に弱くない
I'm not as weak as the you I saw last year.
だってまさか胸が渇くわ
Because, unexpectedly, my heart feels so parched.
実際恋するだけなら誰でもできる
Actually, just falling in love is easy for anyone,
勇気のもとが大切よ
but the source of courage is what's important.
実際恋愛するのってたいへん！
Actually being in a relationship is so tough!
見失わせない
Don't lose sight of it...
夏祭り 手をつなぎ
At the summer festival, holding hands,
花火を見上げて
looking up at the fireworks.
キラキラとまた滲みて
Sparkingly, it blurs once more,
君が言う
and you say...
夕方来て 金魚すくい
"Come by at dusk, let's catch goldfish."
君がさあ びきで
You scooped them up...
なんて恋 夢見てる
What kind of love is this? I'm dreaming!
フリップチューン
Flip tune!
一人きり 家を飛び出て
Alone, running out of the house,
音楽聴いている
listening to music.
意味もなく 涙とか
For no reason, tears and such
出てきちゃう
start coming out.
寂しいよ 寂しいよ
I'm lonely, I'm lonely.
なぜか寂しいよ 凄く恋い
Somehow I'm so lonely, deeply in love,
夢見てる
dreaming!
フリップチューン
Flip tune!
ちょっ！イケロジカってあるんでしょうか？
Wait, is there such a thing as cool logic?
ねえ　君は
Hey, you are...
もどろどろしてちゃ
Got to shake! Shake!
飲み込まれるよ
It will be swallowed up.
都会では
In downtown areas,
愛だ恋だと言いつもりなら
If you mean it when you say "Let's love,"
それなりに
That's right!
男らしくって
Act like a man,
自信ありげで　鮮やかに
Be confident, and be gorgeous!
私たち　それだけで甘えたいと思う
We spoil ourselves with just that,
涙の甘い顔は
A sweet, tearful face...
できない立派なのだ
Is something we can't show guys like you!
君のもとの開いた動きと私の　祭に刻んで　ねえ！
Etched deep into the space between your breath and mine! Hey!
愛してよ　誰にも負けず愛して愛して愛してきて
Love me! Love no one else, just love, love, love me!
安心感　勇気感　それが欲しいの
Confidence and youth, that's what we want!
抱きしめて
Hold me tight!
生まれたまんまの　裸の裸の裸のKISS　この愛が本物と　別れがいいの
Just the way we were born, a naked, naked, naked kiss—is this love real, or are we breaking up?
この愛が本物とわかるように　気付いて
This love is real, so you can tell—just kiss me!
愛してよ　もう一度切符ほど　愛して愛して愛し好きで　少しぐらい　ぐういんで　ちょうどいいのよ
Love me! Just love, love, love me for a little while, it's just right!
抱きしめて
Hold me tight!
生まれたまんまの　裸の裸の裸のKISS　この愛が本物と　別れがいいの
Just the way we were born, a naked, naked, naked kiss—is this love real, or are we breaking up?
この愛が本物とわかるように　気付いて
This love is real, so you can tell—just kiss me!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ　盛れ！　盛れ！アモーレ！
More, my amor! More, more!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
More! More! More! More! More! More!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ　一番の私は私
More! Mi Amore! Number one girl is me!
ありのまになんて　愛してあげない
Saying "just the way you are" won't make me fall in love!
今は涙みたいに　今を
I want you to cry like a baby, right now!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
More! More! More! More! More! More! More!
無垢な瞳はフィルター
Those innocent eyes are filtered!
燃えてゆくいは切ない
Burning away—it's so painful!
想い出なら　綺麗なまま　笑っていられないの
If you miss me, just smile prettily and let me hear you moan!
泣いても笑っても一緒素顔は裏腹
Even when crying, our smiles are mirrored!
速攻かけたあなたにこそ広げ
So rush in and bare it all to you!
今度周りの角度で　悪魔でも味付ける尽くしたの
From a different angle, like a true villain,
ずっと焼き付けて
Burn and scar yourself!
油断できないわ　ショットちゃん
Drop your guard and you're out!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ　私を好きでいさーせてて
More! Mi Amore! I want you to love me like crazy!
ありのまになんて　なんか満足くない
Saying "just the way you are" won't make me easily satisfied!
現実以上　それ以上
More than reality, more!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ　一番の私を見て
More! Mi Amore! Look at the number one girl!
ありのまになんて　愛してあげない
Saying "just the way you are" won't make me fall in love!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
More! More! More! More! More! More!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ　あなたを好きでいさーせてて
More! Mi Amore! I want you to love me like crazy!
愛してよからと　ボボブさながら
Saying "just the way you are" won't make me easily satisfied!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ　私の元を去るのね
More! Mi Amore! I want you to follow my lead!
哀しや育って　心の内は悪い
Tears will flow, but my heart is still petty!
めちゃくちゃにして　話そう
Mess it all up and talk to me!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
More! More! More! More! More! More!
ライライライライ...
Lai lai lai lai...
M-O-R-E-N-O-R-E
ああ！盛り！ミ・アモーレ！
Ah! Mori! Mi-Amore!
Hakos Baelz
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
Raora Panthera
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
今夜は会えそうに　ナイアイアイ
Doesn't look like I'll be able to see you tonight yai yai
不思議と寂しい　アイアイアイ
It's strangely lonely yai yai yai
背伸びをしてる　わけじゃないのに胸が痛い
I'm not trying too hard, but even so my heart aches
仲間が集まって　ガキアツカイ
When you're with your friends, you treat me like a kid
今すぐ大人に　ナリタイアイ
I want to grow up quickly yai
こんなに苦しいのが　初恋ですか？
Is first love supposed to be this painful?
アーケード　走りぬけ
I run through the arcade
信号が青になる
The signal's turning green
あの人が　この時間　ココを通る
He always passes by here at this time
ほら　春紅のスカーレット
Look, spring scarlet
我慢なんてできない
I can't be patient
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition
恋の色が　か・お・る
Love's color is fragrant
yes my love
週末はみんなは　ワイアイアイ
On the weekend, we all get together yai yai
なぜなのあなた　イナイアイアイ
But for some reason you're not here yai yai
こんな日はつまらない　そろそろ帰ろうかな…
Days like this are boring, I guess I'll go home soon...
噂じゃ彼女が　デキタトカ
Rumors say you've got a girlfriend
そんなの全く　キキタクナイ
But I don't want to hear a word of it
張り裂けそうな　くらい頭がナナメ
My head's all twisted like it's about to burst
雨が降る　週末は
It's raining on the weekend
少し街も静か
The streets are a little quiet
このままじゃ　眠れない　せつなすぎる
At this rate I won't be able to sleep, it's too bittersweet
あぁ　春紅のスカーレット
Ah, spring scarlet
そっと近づきたい
I want to get closer
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition
恋の虹が　ひ・か・る
Love's rainbow shines
yes my love
ほら　春紅のスカーレット
Look, spring scarlet
我慢なんてできない
I can't be patient
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition
恋の色が　か・お・る
Love's color is fragrant
yes my love
ほら　春紅のスカーレット
Look, spring scarlet
そっと近づきたい
I want to get closer
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition
恋の虹が　ひ・か・る
Love's rainbow shines
yes my love
with you idoll pride
with me idoll pride
一歩一歩 これからも ずっと二人で
Step by step, from now on, together forever.
good day, bad day it's like a boat rocking
don't worry no matter how slowly
i can sail forward on and on
it's you, it's you giving me voice and life and love
more fantastic than fantasy i can go anywhere
たくさんの「ありがとう」伝わってるし伝えたい
I've received many "thank yous" and I want to convey them,
憧れた遠い背中 少しは近づけたかな？
I wonder if I've gotten closer to that distant back I admired?
笑顔であれ！かわいいあれ！君のために
Be smiling! Be cute! For you,
まだまだ届けたい
I still want to deliver more.
with you idoll pride
with me idoll pride
What's up? I am Chaos, the event horizon,
a stewardess trapped in a cage devised by your best friend.
Bae's taken us from hololive English Promise, witchcraft,
and me, and some goods introduction!
Well, welcome, welcome, welcome. How did you like the song?
It was so hard! Yeah, really.
I never do idol dances. This is—
This is so hard! Ah, is it?
It happens often in HoloPro, but...
Don't understand!
Wait, I remember in the dance lessons you told me about like the different genres...
Yeah, like dance that appeared in this, I was quite surprised.
There's a lot of house.
Ah, this is quite house. This is house? House?
Okay. And then there's also—
There's locking.
You said that's rock?
This is locking.
Oh, you meant locking, not rocking? Oh, locking!
I thought it was a rock dance style. Okay. Now, locking, misunderstanding.
Yeah! That was so hard!
I could tell. Wow, I was so surprised.
I was like, what kind of idol dance has house and locking in the same dance? That's crazy.
They were trying all kinds of things back then.
But yeah, that's from my favorite idol group, BiDEEZ, Kobasolo.
And it's like a pretty old song at this point, but it has this one part in the choreography...
...that I thought would be perfect for like a duo. So I thought, I want to do it with you, together!
Is this part...? Ahahaha! That was so fun!
I really wanted to do it with you. Thank you!
Okay. Um, I have also prepared a little game for us.
A game? A game of camera rush! There's so many cameras, and I would like to make use of it.
We'll play a game where you have to find the camera. Is this the first camera that we're looking for so far? Maybe it's like here... Uh... Yeah!
Found it!
I see, I see, I see. Yay! Okay, Bae, you find the next one. Where is that?
Is it there? Or is it the opposite? Ah, we didn't find it first! No, it's not there! Where is it?
Ah, is it? Is it? Is it? Is it?
If we continue running around, surely we will find the next one.
Wait, hold on. Right there!
Oh! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I see it right there!
Ah! Hello! Hi!
That was really difficult.
Next, where is it? Why do they find these cameras? I see you!
When is this angle ever being used?
Konnichiwa!
One more, one more, one more, one more! Under a disco ball? Wait, I saw their shadow.
Wait, the disco ball should be like... No, no, it's like... No, no. It's not there.
No, it's like... It's hard to be so nice to... Am I looking at it?
Are we looking at it?
Wait, what? One last. Last one? Last one? Last one. Is that the last one?
Well, well, this one's easy because... That's not a challenge!
Hi! Yay! Okay, okay, okay, that was fun!
Well, well, well, well. Yes. This is not the end, though.
What are you doing next? Well, first of all, the various BiDEEZ corner will continue.
One more song, because I love them so much. And for the next one, I have four guests.
Four! And they are none other than Justice, because last year for the Easter hololive project cover song live, I also had them over, but they were like in 2D, like in a paper form.
Oh! Great! So I thought, well, this year I got them all in 3D! Justice!
Yeah. And they will be wearing like a little bit of a costume, a cosplay... a cosplay?
Something like that. A gym costume that matches the music video. So pay attention to what's different.
And with that, I guess, have fun with the rest of the show.
And the next song, which is... Senno-Seishun-Skydive!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
手紙書いていいんだろう?
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
記念に写真とってもいいかい?
Can I take a photo for memory's sake?
ひとめぼれなんだ 僕がはじけた
It's love at first sight, I'm torn apart,
とまらない感覚 これが恋だろう?
This unstoppable feeling, is this love?
君とすれ違う いいにおいがした
As I pass by you, I smell something pleasant,
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be nice to everyone!
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it,
目が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb.
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
But today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I want to be reborn as a microphone.
あいつもライバル 話しかけてる
That person over there is a rival,
湧き起こる感覚 これが嫉妬さ
This feeling that wells up, this is jealousy.
休憩時間に少し会話できた
During breaks, we got to talk a little,
まつげがとても長いね
You have such long eyelashes.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back,
最初の日に戻りたい
I want to go back to the first day.
君に伝えたいことばかり
I've got so much I want to tell you!
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back,
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it,
目が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb.
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
手紙書いていいんだろう?
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
記念にとってもいいか?
Can I take a photo for memory's sake?
ひとめぼれなんだ 僕がはじけた
It's love at first sight, I'm torn apart,
とまらない感覚 これが恋だろう?
This unstoppable feeling, is this love?
君とすれ違う いいにおいがした
As I pass by you, I smell something pleasant,
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be nice to everyone!
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it,
目が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb.
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
もう一度君に会いたいよ
I want to see you once more.
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
手紙書いていいんだろう?
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
記念に写真とってもいいかい?
Can I take a photo for memory's sake?
ひとめぼれなんだ 僕がはじけた
It's love at first sight, I'm torn apart,
とまらない感覚 これが恋だろう?
This unstoppable feeling, is this love?
君とすれ違う いいにおいがした
As I pass by you, I smell something pleasant,
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be nice to everyone!
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it,
目が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb.
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I want to be reborn as a microphone.
あいつもライバル 話しかけてる
That person over there is a rival,
湧き起こる感覚 これが嫉妬さ
This feeling that wells up, this is jealousy.
休憩時間に少し会話できた
During breaks, we got to talk a little,
まつげがとても長いね
You have such long eyelashes.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back,
最初の日に戻りたい
I want to go back to the first day.
君に伝えたいことばかり
I've got so much I want to tell you!
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back,
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it,
目が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb.
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
手紙書いていいんだろう?
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
記念に写真とってもいいかい?
Can I take a photo for memory's sake?
ひとめぼれなんだ 僕がはじけた
It's love at first sight, I'm torn apart,
とまらない感覚 これが恋だろう?
This unstoppable feeling, is this love?
君とすれ違う いいにおいがした
As I pass by you, I smell something pleasant,
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be nice to everyone!
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it,
目が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb.
独り占めにしたいんだ
I want you all to myself,
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts,
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Young bus guide, you're so dazzling,
もう一度君に会いたいよ
I want to see you once more.
どうたらこうたら 言い訳してる
No matter how you put it, you're making excuses,
イライラくるんなぁ
You're getting nervous, huh?
あの子が良いなら
If that girl's so great,
そっち行けばいいじゃん
Why don't you just go with her?
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special Generation!
どうたらこうたら言い訳してる
No matter how you put it, you're making excuses,
イライラくるんなぁ
You're getting nervous, huh?
あの子が良いなら
If that girl's so great,
そっち行けばいいじゃん
Why don't you just go with her?
チャラチャラチャラチャラシバーつけて
Dressed up all flashily,
フラフラしてて
Staggering about,
誰にアピってるの?
Who are you trying to appeal to?
余所見なんて許さないわよ
I won't forgive you for looking away.
好きと 好きと 好きと
"I love you, I love you, I love you,"
好きと言いなさい そう この場で
Please say "I love you," yes, right here!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special Generation!
LOVE 運命を信じたい
I believe in fate.
100万年過ぎたって
Even if a million years pass,
この愛は ゆ・る・ぎ・ない
This love is f-i-r-m!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special Generation!
LOVE 嫌いにもなれないわ
I don't hate you yet.
地下鉄の中だって
Even in the subway,
過去よりも あ・い・し・て!
More so than you have in the past, l-o-v-e m-e!
会ったら会ったで
When we're together,
どこに行くでも
No matter where we go,
ダラダラしてる
It seems like it takes forever.
私が決めないと
If I don't make a decision,
なにも始まらない
Nothing is going to start happening.
押したり引いたりなんて
Pushing and pulling,
器用にする 事 出来ない
I just can't seem to get good at it.
まっすぐ行くだけよ
I just move straight ahead,
誰も 彼も 驚くような
It's like everyone is surprised.
熱い 愛で 私私抱きしめて
Embrace me with a passionate love!
An! Hold on my love
Oi!
Wow wow yeah
どうしたりこうたり 言い訳してる
Doing this and that, making excuses,
イライラくるなぁ
It's so irritating, huh?
あの子がいいなら
If that girl's so great,
そっち行けばいいじゃん
Why don't you just go with her?
チャラチャラチャラチャラ
Flaunting around all flashily,
シルバーつけて
Wearing silver accessories,
フラフラしてんの
Staggering all around.
誰にアピールしてるの？
Who are you trying to appeal to?
よそ見なんて許さないわよ
I won't forgive you for looking away!
好きと好きと好きと言いなさいそうこの場で
Love, love, love, say you love me right here!
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
運命を信じたい
I want to believe in fate,
百万年過ぎたってこの愛は揺るがない
Even if a million years pass, this love won't waver.
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
嫌いにもなれないわ
I can't even bring myself to hate you,
地下鉄の中だって
Even in the subway,
過去より愛して！
Love me more than ever before!
Oi!
Wow wow yeah
あっつあつで
With burning passion,
どこに行くでも
No matter where we go,
ダラダラしてる
Lounging around lazily.
私が決めなきゃ
If I don't make the decision,
何も始まらない
Nothing will ever start.
押したり引いたりなんて器用に
Pushing and pulling so skillfully
することができない
is something I just can't do.
まっすぐ行くだけよ
I'll just keep moving straight ahead!
誰も彼も驚くような
With a passionate love that will shock everyone,
熱い愛で私私抱きしめて
Hold me, hold me tight in your arms!
あん！Hold on my love
Ah! Hold on my love
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
孤独など感じない
I don't feel any loneliness,
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は永遠
This love will last forever.
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
離れない離さない
We won't part, I won't let go,
昨日よりも今よりもまた明日も愛して！
Love me more than yesterday, today, and tomorrow too!
Oi!
Wow wow yeah
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
孤独など感じない
I don't feel any loneliness,
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は永遠
This love will last forever.
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
離れない離さない
We won't part, I won't let go,
昨日よりも今よりもまた明日も愛して！
Love me more than yesterday, today, and tomorrow too!
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
孤独など感じない
I don't feel any loneliness,
池袋過ぎたって
Even past Ikebukuro,
この愛は永遠
This love will last forever.
スペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation Love!
離れない離さない
We won't part, I won't let go,
昨日よりも今よりもまた明日も愛して！
Love me more than yesterday, today, and tomorrow too!
Oi!
Wow wow yeah
スペシャルジェネレーション
Special Generation!
Thank you so much, everybody!
Thank you for coming! Thank you for watching!
Bye-bye!
Announcement announcement!
Takanashi Kiara Birthday Merchandise 2026!
Here is the banner.
First of all, the big item that is the main character is...
First of all, the big item that features the main character...
抱き枕カバーだ！やっとやった！ after so many years of doing merchandise...
is a body pillow cover! I finally did it after so many years of doing merch.
KFP don't leave me hanging, leave me laying on the bed, yeah!
So I did something I originally never thought I would do. KFP, don't leave me hanging—leave me lying on the bed, yeah!
一つ目のアイテムはなんと！抱き枕カバーです！
The first item is... a body pillow cover!
きんばい！
Yay!
Next, we have a really cute plushy set of my kitty kays, Smoothie and Chonkers.
Next, we have a really cute plushie set of my kitty cats, Smoothie and Chonkers.
They're so cute and fluffy, and I can bring them everywhere now! unusual too, you can hang them on your bag or keys.
They're so cute and fluffy, and I can bring them everywhere now! And as usual, you can hang them on your bag or keys.
私の寝子のぬいぐるみセットでキーホルダーなどとして使えます。どこにでも連れてってあげてください。
These are my cat plushies that can be used as keychains. Please take them everywhere with you!
Next one is these badges, but they are a bit unusual because this time they are square and made from fake leather...
Next are these badges. They're a bit unusual because they're square and made of fake leather, so they're a bit squishy. And of course, you can make an ita-bag with these too.
今回のバッチはなんと！フェイクレザーでできてますし、あと四角い変わったおバッジておりますが...
These badges are square and made of fake leather! They're quite unique, but of course, you can use them to make an ita-bag too.
Last item is the smartphone ring, modeled after KFP chickens. Maybe this way holding your phones won't be as hard with your wings. Cute!
The last item is the smartphone ring, modeled after KFP chickens. Maybe this way holding your phone won't be as hard with your wings. Cute!
最後のアイテムはスマホリング。もちろんKFPモチーフです。
The last item is a smartphone ring, of course featuring the KFP motif.
Besides that, there's also advice pack! I haven't been doing any voice packs these past months, so make sure to get this one, rare!
Besides that, there's also a voice pack! I haven't done any voice packs in recent months, so make sure to grab this rare one!
そのほかにには久しぶりにボイスもあります。最近あんまり参加してないのでぜひこの機会に、お願いします！
And there's also a voice pack for the first time in a while! I haven't participated in a while, so please take this opportunity to get it!
If you get the full set, then you receive
a Polaroid from me alongside it,
and if you're lucky to get the limited one, then it will be signed by my own hands.
もちろん、いつも通りフルセットをゲットすると、え、ま、チェキ付いてきます。
Of course, as usual, if you get the full set, it comes with a photo card.
限定版だとう、キアラのサイン入りですね。よろしくお願いします。
The limited edition comes with Kiara's signature. Thank you for your support!
And one more thing, before we end, I have a super awesome song cover coming up right after this!
このあとは韓国のVTuberアイドルIDJとのコラボ歌ってみたプレミア公開しますので、見てください！
After this, we'll premiere our collaboration cover song with Korean VTuber IDJ, so check it out!
And we'll try our best to raid into it, but if it does not work out, please make your way there on your own.
And we'll try our best to raid into it, but if it doesn't work out, please make your way there on your own.
Besides that, thank you so much for celebrating my birthday today!
I worked so hard on this and I'm really proud.
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you can, get the merchandise! And in German we say, "Auf Wiedersehen!"
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you can, get the merch! And in German we say, "Auf Wiedersehen!"
最後に、今日は お誕生日をお祝いに来てくれてありがとうございました！本当にいろいろ努力して来たのです。
Lastly, thank you so much for coming to celebrate my birthday today! I've really worked hard on various things.
コメントと、いいね、そしてもしよかったらグッズもよろしくお願いいたします。
Comments, likes, and if you'd like, the merchandise as well, please check them out!
ではでは、Auf Wiedersehen! See you in the song cover!
Well then, Auf Wiedersehen! See you in the song cover!